<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>dumosuku</title><subtitle>I'm not good at CSS.</subtitle> <updated>2022-11-24T00:08:06-08:00</updated> <author> <name>Derrick Tran</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 Derrick Tran </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Hacktober - SWIFT's Month of SCARE</title><link href="/posts/Hacktober/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hacktober - SWIFT's Month of SCARE" /><published>2022-11-02T00:00:00-07:00</published> <updated>2022-11-23T21:39:47-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Hacktober/</id> <content src="/posts/Hacktober/" /> <author> <name>Derrick</name> </author> <category term="Blog" /> <summary> This past October, SWIFT has celebrated the National Cyber Security Awareness Month by hosting what we call Hacktober! So usually here at SWIFT, we teach all sorts of topics ranging from Windows/Linux security to the basics of the CI/CD pipeline. For October in particular, we focused solely on hacking hence the name, Hacktober. I even got to lead my first SWIFT workshop regarding web applicat... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>HackTheBox - The Progression</title><link href="/posts/HackTheBox/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HackTheBox - The Progression" /><published>2022-10-15T00:00:00-07:00</published> <updated>2022-11-23T21:37:54-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/HackTheBox/</id> <content src="/posts/HackTheBox/" /> <author> <name>Derrick</name> </author> <category term="Blog" /> <summary> HackTheBox, or HTB for short, is a website that I have used to develop a general penetration testing methodology. The platform provides you with multiple intentionally vulnerable hosts with the intent for you to compromise them. Each machine is effectively a long CTF where you embark on a journey to exploit vulnerabilities to gain flags hidden on the system. Every system provides you with a u... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>CPP Cyber Bootcamps 2022 - The Throw of the Year</title><link href="/posts/CPPCyberBootcamps2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CPP Cyber Bootcamps 2022 - The Throw of the Year" /><published>2022-08-27T00:00:00-07:00</published> <updated>2022-08-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated> <id>/posts/CPPCyberBootcamps2022/</id> <content src="/posts/CPPCyberBootcamps2022/" /> <author> <name>Derrick</name> </author> <category term="Blog" /> <summary> CPP Cyber is the competition team here at California State Polytechnic University, Pomona. Only skilled individuals are allowed to make it onto the team and CPP Cyber helps you with that by hosting these rigorous bootcamps to teach you the skills necessary to join the team. I have participated in the bootcamp in the year prior however, I did not take it seriously and paid the consequences by ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>RvB Spring 2022 - A Duo Is All It Takes</title><link href="/posts/RvBSpring2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="RvB Spring 2022 - A Duo Is All It Takes" /><published>2022-04-18T00:00:00-07:00</published> <updated>2022-11-23T21:37:54-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/RvBSpring2022/</id> <content src="/posts/RvBSpring2022/" /> <author> <name>Derrick</name> </author> <category term="Blog" /> <summary> Red versus Blue, more commonly referred to as RvB, is an event held by SWIFT every semester. During this competition, you, the player, can sign up with up to 3 other people to form a squad of 4. With your squad, you are given a network of X amount of boxes to secure and defend as an active red team attempts to break in and take down your services. Meanwhile all of this chaos is brewing, the m... </summary> </entry> </feed>
